Guide to the Paul Horgan Papers
Beinecke Rare Book and Manuscript Library
- March 1999 Acquisition, 1942-1976; 5.75; (8 boxes)
  - Fast Company, undated (Box 212)
  - Unidentified short story, undated (Box 212)
  - Short stories, undated (Box 212)
  - Lamy Memorial, 1950 (Box 212)
  - Notebooks, undated; 2 (Box 212)
  - The Curvature of the Earth, undated (Box 212)
  - The Man on the Playroom Floor, undated (Box 212)
  - American Adventure, undated (Box 212)
  - The Paris Feeling, undated (Box 212)
  - National Honeymoon, undated (Box 212)
  - The One Who Wouldn't Dance, undated (Box 212)
  - Horgan lecture posters, undated (Box 213)
  - Biographical material, 1951-1975; 3 (Box 213)
  - Photographs of Paul Horgan, undated (Box 214 (Oversize))
  - Unidentified artwork (Box 215 (Roll))
- February 2004 Acquisition, 1985; (1 folder)
  Former call number Uncat ZA File 682
  - Clara Hughes: typescript (photocopy), annotated, with manuscript note to Joseph Reed, 1985 (Box 216)
- June 2004 Acquisition, 1983-1985; 0.42; (1 box)
  Former call number Uncat MSS 659
  - Clerihews of Paul Horgan, 1983-1985
    - Correspondence, 1983-1984 (Box 216)
    - Paste-ups, section one, 1985; 2 (Box 216)
    - Paste-ups, section two, 1985; 2 (Box 216)
    - Paste-ups, section three, 1985; 2 (Box 216)
    - Original illustrations, 1985; 2 (Box 216)
    - Layout designs, 1985 (Box 216)
    - Cover designs, undated (Box 216)
    - Typed manuscript, annotated, undated (Box 216)
    - Final text and cover, 1985 (Box 216)
    - Notes, undated (Box 216)
- June 2006 Acquisition, 1974-1976; 0.21; (1 box)
  Former call number Uncat MSS 874
  - Thin Mountain Air, galley proof, with reviews; letters to Martin Griffin from Paul Horgan; and other papers by or relating to Paul Horgan, 1974-1976; 6 (Box 217)
- September 2013 Acquisition, 1939-1992, undated; 0.83; (2 boxes)
  - Writings
    - Marche Militaire, chapter one, undated (Box 218)
    - Marche Militaire, chapter two, undated (Box 218)
    - Marche Militaire, chapter three, undated (Box 218)
    - Leadership, undated (Box 218)
    - Pilgrimage, 1992 (Box 218)
    - Brief Lives, undated (Box 218)
    - Narrow Escapes in the Pentagon, undated (Box 218)
    - By Firelight, undated (Box 218)
    - After the Duck Hunt, undated (Box 219)
    - Publisher's List, undated (Box 219)
    - Publisher's List, proofs, undated (Box 219)
    - Worlds and Tempests, undated (Box 219)
    - A Tree on the Plains, undated (Box 219)
    - Proem, undated (Box 219)
    - Biographical materials, undated (Box 219)
    - The Young Robert Oppenheimer In Summer, undated (Box 219)
  - Printed material, 1939-1976; 2 (Box 219)